（加利福尼亚 旧金山）
嗨 麦迪
Hey, Maddy.
你瞧 呃 我并不想扫你的兴
Listen, I, uh, hate to pull you away…
但是你得和我一起回趟办公室
but I'm gonna need you to come back to the office with me.
- 真的吗？- 是啊 因为我要在天亮前
- Really? Yeah, turns out I gotta file…
- 把计算机里的档案整理好 - 半夜
- …those docs by midnight and-Midnight?
我需要你… 呃
Yeah, I'm gonna need you to, um…
- 这没用 是吧？- 不 并没有 内森
- This isn't working at all, is it? - No, it's not, Nate.
听着 我多喝了几杯 我开不了车了
Listen, I've had a couple. I shouldn't really drive.
- 能送我回去吗 - 我已经给你叫了车了
- Could you just give me a lift-? - I already called you a cab.
明早见
I'll see you in the morning.
- 你经常遇到这种事？- 只有在以Y字结尾的日子才会有
- Hmm, that happen a lot? - Only on the days that end with a Y.
你还好吗？
You okay?
是的
Yeah.
我得走了
I've gotta go.
[邪恶力量 第2季第17集]
这就是了 警探
Here he is, detective.
咬得真够狠的
That's a pretty nasty bite.
你知道是什么咬的他吗？
You know what bit him?
我还不大确定
I haven't quite determined that just yet.
说吧 医生 不作记录
Come on, doc, off the record.
- 好吧 绝对不能记录在案 - 好的
- Okay, way, way off the record. - Sure.
如果我没有猜错的话 我觉得这个家伙是被狼袭击了
If I didn't know better, I'd say the guy was attacked by a wolf.
除非是动物园丢了一只大灰狼 不然我会说是美洲嚣犬
But unless the zoo is missing one of their lobos, I'm going with pit bull.
- 我喜欢我的工作 - 是啊 我知道
- I like my job. - Yeah, I hear you.
还有件事 这个家伙
One more thing. This guy…
他的心脏是不是没了？
was his heart missing?
是的 你怎么知道？我的报告还没写完呢
Yeah, how did you know that? I haven't even finished my report.
猜的
Lucky guess.
这个律师 是这里头一个没有心脏的死人吗？
This lawyer guy the first heart-free corpse in town?
头一个男人
First man.
去年也有几个女人先后失踪
Over the past year, several women have gone missing.
后来在水湾发现了尸体
Their bodies all washed up later in the bay…
被腐蚀的太严重 无法鉴别细节
too deteriorated to draw firm conclusions.
- 但都没有心脏 - 没有
- But no hearts? - No hearts.
她们都是在亨特地段附近工作的妓女
All hookers working at Hunter's Point.
警方想把这些事保持低调 但他们找的是连环杀手
Cops are trying to keep things under wrap. They're looking for a serial killer.
是在月圆之时？
And the lunar cycle?
对 每个月 每一次谋杀都发生在满月的那周
Yeah, all the murders happened in the week leading up to the full moon.
- 这周就是 - 被害的是这个律师
- Which is this week, right? - Hence the lawyer.
好极了
Awesome.
迪恩 你能别那么幸灾乐祸吗？
Dean, could you be a bigger geek about this?
抱歉 但这种白天是人
I'm sorry, man, but what about a human by day…
晚上变成杀人机器的怪物 你不明白吗？
a freak animal killing machine by moonlight don't you understand?
吸血狼人可都是变态
I mean, werewolves are badass.
从小到大我们连一只都没见过
We haven't seen one since we were kids.
好吧 万事通 你知道么
Okay, sparky, and you know what?
- 等我们杀了它 我们可以去迪斯尼 - 知道最棒的是什么么？
- After we kill it, we can go to Disneyland. - Know what the best part is?
我们已经知道了消灭这些东西的办法
We already know how to bring these suckers down.
只要这些小家伙穿透他们心脏就行了
One of these bad boys right to the heart.
- 那我们接下来怎么做？- 和发现尸体的女孩聊聊
- What's our next move? - Talk to the girl who found the body.
我不明白 我已经做过笔录了
I don't understand. I already gave my statement.
还有一些事有待核实
Right. Yeah, well, we just need to verify a few things.
这是我的邻居格伦 格伦 这位是警长…
This is my neighbor, Glen. Glen, this is detective-
兰迪斯 还有但丁警长
Landis. And Detective Dante.
好吧 我看我得走了
Well, guess I'll leave you to it.
好的 谢谢你的菜
Okay. Thanks for the casserole.
考虑的真周到
Oh, how thoughtful.
有什么需要尽管说
Just call if you need anything.
他人挺不错 他过来看看我
He's sweet. He came over to check on me.
请 请坐
Have-Have a seat.
你一定受了很大惊吓
You must be pretty shaken up.
- 你是内森·马利根的助理吧？- 是啊 2年了
- You were Nate Mulligan's assistant, right? - For two years, yeah.
你很了解他这个人吧
So you knew all about him?
可能比他自己还要了解 内森他…
Probably knew more about him than he did.
他人挺好
Nate was-He was nice.
- 但是 - 其实没什么
- But? - Nothing really, I…
他一喝多了 就容易随便
He had a few scotches and started hitting on anyone…
找人搭讪 你了解那种人
in a five-mile radius. You know the type.
是啊 我很了解
Yeah. I do, actually.
他有什么仇人吗？
Did he have any enemies?
你什么意思？当然 看起来就是动物袭击造成的
What do you mean? It sure looked like an animal attack.
不 我们只是想排除一切可能性 有人怨恨他吗？
No. Yeah, we're just covering all the bases. Anyone that might've had a beef with him?
- 前客户 或者前… - 什么？
- Former client, an ex? - What?
有点尴尬 我的前男友 库尔特
This is embarrassing but my ex-boyfriend, Kurt.
他姓什么？
Kurt have a last name?
米勒 我们分手之后 他就疯疯癫癫的
Mueller. After we broke up, he went kind of nuts.
他…
He's…
他一直在跟踪我
Well, he's kind of been stalking me.
他觉得我和内森之间有私情
He got it in his head that something was going on between Nate and I.
- 他去过我的办公室 - 然后呢？
- He showed up at my office. - What happened?
库尔特找到内森 打了他 然后被保安制止了
Kurt got into it with Nate. Threw a punch before security grabbed him.
- 我很走运 没被开除 - 你最后一次见到库尔特是什么时候？
- I was lucky to keep my job. - When was the last time you saw Kurt?
几天前的晚上 实际上 就是内森死的那天晚上
A few nights ago. Actually, the night Nate died.
我们在酒吧喝酒 然后库尔特来了
We were grabbing drinks at this bar and Kurt showed up.
- 然后呢？- 没什么
- And? - Nothing.
只是… 他好像在盯着我看
It was like he was watching me.
后来就走了
Then he was gone.
实话说吧
To tell you the truth…
我很害怕
he scares me.
你觉得呢？
So, what do you think?
前男友是个跟踪狂 他恨那个老板
Stalker ex-boyfriend? He hates the boss.
- 那晚他也在那儿 - 你觉得他就是我们要找的狼人？
- And he was there that night. - You think he's our dog-faced boy?
可以这么说
Well, it's a theory.
- 更糟的我们都遇过 - 是啊
- We've had worse. - Yeah.
我们去查查库尔特吧？
What do you say we pay Kurt a visit?
- 有发现吗？- 除了剩饭就是餐盒
- Anything? - Nothing but leftovers and a six pack.
看看冷冻箱里吧
Check the freezer.
没准儿在哈根达斯什么的后面 能找到人的心脏
Maybe there's some human hearts behind the H?agen-Dazs or something.
萨姆 过来看看
Sam, come here.
看这个
Check it out.
有人在那吗？
Is somebody there?
我去报警
I'll call 911.
我得说 库尔特越来越像我们要找的狼人了
I'd say Kurt's looking more and more like our Cujo.
他就在这附近 我们最好去看看麦迪逊
Dean, if he's out here, we better check on Madison.
- 出什么事了？- 警方调查 格伦
- What's going on? - Police business, Glen.
怎么了？
What is it?
我们能私下谈谈吗？
Well, maybe we should talk privately?
库尔特有没有来过这儿？
Has Kurt been here?
不算吧
Not exactly.
不算吧 到底是有还是没有？他昨晚在外面
- What exactly does "not exactly" mean? Well, he was outside last night.
就只是看着
Just looking.
望着我看
Just looking at me.
他做了什么事吗？
Has he done something?
- 我们不大清楚 - 可能什么事都没有
- We're not really sure. It's probably nothing.
但是… 我们不想冒任何风险
But we just don't wanna take any chances.
事实上 我们中的一人应该留下和你在一起 以防他过来
In fact, one of us should probably stay here with you, just in case he stops by.
- 他在哪儿上班？- 他自己有家汽车修理厂
- Where does he work? - He owns a body shop.
你能给我们一个地址吗？
You mind grabbing that address for us?
谢谢
Thanks.
- 好的 你去吧 我留下 - 算了吧 你去追踪那个变态前男友
- All right. You go, I'll stay. - Forget that. You go after the creepy ex.
- 我要在这里陪美女 - 为什么总是你和女孩在一起？
- I'll hang here with the hot chick. - Why do you always hang with the girls?
因为我比你年长
Because I'm older.
算了 我们用老办法解决这个问题
No. Screw that. We settle this the old-fashioned way.
迪恩 你总是出剪刀
Dean, always with the scissors.
得了 得了 三局两胜
Shut up. Shut up. Two out of three.
- 该死 - 搞定它 好吧
- God! - Bundle up out there, all right?
- 你想去沙发那坐吗？- 不 不用了
- Um, do you wanna sit on the couch? - No. No, no, I'm okay.
- 那里更舒服一些 - 呃 我很好
- It's more comfortable. - Aw, I'm fine.
我看我还是到沙发上坐吧
You know what? I think I will sit on that couch.
我猜猜 你正在她沙发上坐着
Let me guess. You're sitting on her couch like a stiff…
- 想着怎么找点话题开场 - 你找到库尔特了？
- …trying to think of something to say. - You find Kurt?
他整周都在上班 但是由于我很强
He hasn't been at work. But because I'm good…
我的意思是 非常 非常强 我知道他可能在哪儿了
and I mean really, really good, I got a line on where he might be.
- 她穿的什么？- 再见 迪恩
- What's she wearing? - Bye, Dean.
哦 萨姆
Oh, Sammy.
你不爱他 你想做的就是回到我身边…
You don't love him. All you wanna do is get back at me…
带走一切
and take away everything.
它是否曾经在你的大脑中穿行
Has it ever run through your thick brain…
不是所有的事都是关于你的？
that not everything is about you?
- 我看见了 - 什么？
- I saw that. - What?
看见什么？
Saw what?
好吧 这么说吧
Okay, this is the deal:
我的家 我的电视
My house, my TV.
由我决定看什么
I never get to watch my show…
忍了吧
so suck it up.
等一下 金德尔嫁给了伊桑的爸爸 只是为了报复他？
Wait, so Kendall married Ethan's father just to get back at him?
她现在得到了所有
Yup. And now she's set to inherit all the casinos…
原本属于伊桑的赌场 真是个贱人
- …that were supposed to go to Ethan. - What a bitch.
承认吧 你入戏了
Admit it, you're hooked.
不 不 不 我… 我才没有
No, no, no. I…I wouldn't say I'm hooked.
我能问你个问题吗？
Can I ask you a question?
有点 有点私人
It's-It's a little personal.
你连我所有的内衣都见识过了
You've seen my entire underwear collection.
问吧
Go ahead.
好 嗯
Okay, um…
你 你很聪明
Well, you're…
我的意思是 你的房子里全是书 你明白吗？
You're clearly smart. I mean, your house is full of great books, you know…
- 你还很独立 - 是啊
- …and you're independent. - Uh-huh.
你怎么会和库尔特在一起？
What were you doing with Kurt?
我不知道
I don't know.
我的意思是 不是说他是这样介绍自己的
I mean, it's not like he introduced himself, like:
「你好 我占有欲极强 我还喜欢打人」
"Hi, I'm possessive and controlling, and I like to punch people.
「能当我女朋友吗？」
Wanna be my girlfriend?"
是啊 我想我们都会犯错的
Yeah, well, I guess we all make mistakes.
是啊 他都被警察通缉了
Yeah, well, mine's wanted by the police.
你真的想知道我为什么和他在一起吗？
You wanna know why I stayed with him? Really?
我很没有安全感
I was too insecure to leave.
我不相信
I find that hard to believe.
- 你看起来不像那个类型的 - 是啊 发生了一些事
- I mean, you don't really seem like the type. - Yeah, well, some stuff happened.
我改变了生活方式 也改变了自己 我觉得变得更好了
My life changed. I changed for the better, I think.
- 出什么事了？- 发生了一件事 我被打劫了
- What happened? - Well, for one thing, I got mugged.
- 那是件好事儿？- 我知道 听起来很怪
- And that's supposed to be a good thing? - I know. It sounds strange.
别误会我 那真的让我很不爽
And don't get me wrong, it rattled me…
然后我突然醒悟了
but then it hit me:
我是要一直自我怜悯 还是去把握自己的生活
I could keep feeling sorry for myself, or I could take control of my life.
我选择了后者
I chose the latter.
- 然后我做的第一件事就是让库尔特离开 - 做的好
- First thing I did was tell Kurt he had to go. - Smart move.
是的
Apparently.
所有事就此明了了
Everything else just opened up, blossomed.
那样真的很好
It's all been wonderful, really.
你想说什么？
What?
大家认为在暴力事件中随机受到伤害
Doesn't everybody think being a victim of random violence…
不是件好事吗？
is the best thing that ever happened to them?
是啊 不尽然
Ha, ha. Yeah, not so much.
你…
You're…
不一般
unusual.
像那种不一般
Unusual like…
- 不正常？- 不 不 不 不
- …unusual? - No. No. No, no, no.
是那种
Unusual like…
令人印象深刻
impressive.
令人难忘 是吗？
You think so?
抱歉
Sorry.
- 嘿 - 我找到他了
- Hey. - I found him.
好的 别放过他
Good. Don't take your eyes off him.
当然 我的眼睛都粘在这儿了
Oh, yeah. My eyes are glued.
萨姆 我得走了
Look, Sammy, I gotta let you go. I, uh-
我 我可不想错过任何事
I don't wanna miss anything.
那么…
So, um…
我去睡觉了
I'm gonna turn in.
好的 我就在这儿
Okay. Yeah. Well, I'll be here.
好
Okay.
你知道… 如果你听见什么或者醒了
You know what? If you hear anything-I mean, if you wake up, just…
就喊我
Just call out.
- 好的 - 好的
- Okay. - Okay.
什么
What the…?
- 迪恩 你还好吗？- 没事 至少我还有意识
Dean.You okay? - Now that I'm conscious.
狼人打晕了我 萨姆 是麦迪逊
The werewolf knocked me out. Sam, it's Madison.
什么？
What?
是啊 牢牢地盯着她
Yeah, awesome job of keeping an eye on her.
迪恩 我一直在这儿 她现在在睡觉
Dean.I've been here the whole time. She's in bed, asleep.
一小时前她可不是
Well, she wasn't an hour ago.
看看她的右臂 我用银刀刺了她
Check her right arm below her elbow. I nicked her with a silver knife.
早上好
Morning.
我的睡衣在哪儿？
Um, where are my pajamas?
萨姆？
Sam?
怎么了？
What's going on?
你去哪儿？
Where are you going?
我哪儿也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
你也一样
And neither are you.
你疯了
You're psychotic.
还骗我是警察 天 我怎么这么傻
The whole "I'm a cop" trip. God, I am so stupid.
看来我们两个都跟自己说的不一样 是吧？
I guess neither of us are who we said we were, huh?
萨姆 你疯了
Sam, you're sick, okay?
你在胡思乱想
You're imagining things.
- 怪物是不存在的 - 你知道什么
- Monsters don't exist, not really. - You know what?
少装了
Save the act.
我没有装
It's not an act.
我不是狼人 那种东西根本不存在
I am not a werewolf. There is no such thing.
那都是假的好不好？
It's made up, all right?
他们不是真的 你知道的
They're not real. You know they're not real.
- 不是？那这伤口从哪儿来的？- 我不知道
- No? Then where did that come from? - I don't know.
萨姆 天啊 你需要帮助
Sam, God, you need help.
求求你 别做会让你后悔的事
Please, don't do something that you're gonna regret.
我不是你想的那种东西
I'm not what you think I am.
我不是
I'm not.
你好吗？
How you doing?
我的头感觉好极了 谢了
My head feels great, thanks.
我们得谈谈
We gotta talk.
她说不知道我说的是什么意思
She says she has no idea what I'm talking about.
- 她在骗人 - 也许吧 也许她真的不知道自己是狼人
- She's lying. - Maybe she doesn't know she's changing.
也许变成狼人的时候 她就失去了意识
Maybe when the creature takes over, she blacks out.
就像个惹火的绿巨人？老弟 她杀了她老板和前男友
Like a really hot Incredible Hulk? She ganked her boss and her ex-boyfriend.
- 听起来可不像是没有意识 - 可如果是真的呢 迪恩？
- That doesn't sound rash and unconscious. - But what if it was?Dean.
如果她大脑里狼人的部分 把那两个人当成威胁？
What if some animal part of her brain saw those guys as threats?
- 见鬼 那个警察肯定也是 - 你什么时候变成狗语者了？
- The cop too. - Are you the dog whisperer now?
我只是…
Look, man, I just…
我不知道 她眼睛里有某种东西
I don't know. There was something in her eyes.
- 是啊 她在杀人 - 可如果她不能控制自己
- Yeah, she's killing people. - But if she has no control-
她当然不能控制
Exactly, she can't control it.
就算她说的是真话 也没什么不同
If she's telling the truth, it won't change anything.
我可不会对一个什么都不知道的女孩开枪
I'm not putting a bullet through some girl's chest.
- 她是怪物 你同情她？- 也许我只是理解她
- She's a monster and you're feeling sorry? - Maybe I understand her.
也许有别的办法完成这活儿
Look.There might be another way we can get the job
而不用杀了她
done without having to waste her.
你是不是跟我想到一起去了？
Are you thinking what I think you're thinking?
爸爸的理论
Dad's theory:
如果杀了咬你的狼人 切断血脉源 也许就能解除变狼朮
"Lycanthropy might have a cure if you kill the werewolf who bit you…
- 也许就能 - 就是鬼才知道的意思 谁知道
- …severing the bloodline. - Might have a cure.Meaning who knows?
- 值得一试 - 我们根本不知道从何开始
- It's worth a shot. - We don't know where to start looking.
咬了她的那狗东西 也许是任何人 可能在任何地方
The puppy that bit her could be anyone, anywhere.
也许已经过了好几年
Could have been years ago.
不 我不觉得
No, I don't think so.
麦迪逊…
Madison.
你是什么时候被打劫的？
When were you mugged?
求你了 这很重要 回答我的问题
Please. It's important, all right? Just answer the question.
大约一个月以前
About a month ago.
- 你看到犯人了么？- 没有
- Did you see the guy? - No.
- 他从后面抓住我 - 他是不是咬了你？
- Grabbed me from behind. - Did he bite you?
你怎么知道？
How did you know that?
- 在哪儿？- 在脖子后面
- Where? - On the back of my neck.
哦 是个爱的齿痕
Well, that was just a love bite.
相信我 比那更糟
Believe me, that could have been a lot worse.
- 你是在哪儿被袭击的？- 从一个朋友那里回家的路上
- Where were you at the time? - Walking home from a friend's loft.
我猜
Let me guess:
离亨特地段不远？
Not too far from Hunter's Point?
和那些凶杀发生地一样
Same place where those other murders happened.
那里肯定就是狼人的狩猎场
I'm telling you, it's a werewolf's hunting grounds.
- 也许吧 但今晚它不一定会去那儿 - 今天正是月圆之夜
- Maybe.That doesn't mean it'll be out tonight. - It's the right time in the lunar cycle.
我知道希望不大
I know it's a long shot.
你还忘了另一件事 麦迪可能很快就会变身
You're forgetting something. Maddy's probably gonna turn soon.
总不能放她出去随便吃人
We can't just let her take off to an all-you-can-eat buffet.
- 我会和她呆在一起 - 如果她挣脱了？
- I'll stay with her. - And if she busts loose?
- 萨姆？- 我会动手
- Sam? - I'll do it.
- 萨姆 - 我会开枪的
- Sam. - I'll shoot her, all right?
不过 迪恩 我要你去那里 至少去找找那个狼人
But, Dean, I need you to go out there. At least go look for the thing.
迪恩 求你了 我们能救这个女孩
Dean, please. We can save this girl.
好吧
Fine.
求你了
Please.
放开我吧
Just let me go.
你看…
Look.
我知道你很害怕
I know you're scared.
我也知道 你决不会相信我的话
I also know that there's no way in hell you're gonna believe me.
但我这么做… 是因为我想要帮你
But I'm doing this because I'm trying to help you.
我不想骗你 我们并不想搞成这样
I'm not gonna lie. The odds aren't exactly in our favor.
但如果能像我祈祷的一样顺利…
But if this goes the way I pray it does…
我会给你松绑
I'll untie you…
我会走出这扇门 永远不再回来
and I'll walk out that door and I'll never come back.
你会继续过你的生活…
You'll live the rest of your life…
而我只是一段不愉快的回忆
and I'll just be a bad memory.
嘿
Hey!
嘿 别告诉别人
Hey, don't mention it.
怎么了？
What happened?
这是哪儿？
Where am I?
救 救救我
Unh. Help-Help me.
我的天 哦 天哪
Oh, God. Oh, my God.
放松 格伦 别害怕
All right, easy, Glen. Just take it easy.
都结束了
It should be over now.
你不会再见到我
You'll never see me again.
说真的 有点悲惨
It was sort of sad, actually.
格伦根本不知道出了什么事
Glen had no clue what was going on.
你说他为什么不杀了麦迪逊 而是把她变成同类？
Why do you think he turned Madison, instead of just killing her?
不知道
I don't know.
- 他看起来对她有点意思 - 也可能是因为他本性善良
- He kind of seemed to have a thing for her. - Maybe his primal instinct did too.
也许只是某种强烈的繁殖行为
Maybe he was looking for a little hot breeding action.
是啊 类似那种的
Yeah. Something like that.
然后呢？
So?
- 然后什么？- 说到麦迪逊…
- So, what? - Speaking of Madison.
- 哦 行了 - 什么行了 你喜欢她 也许 呃
- Oh, whatever. - Don't whatever me. You liked her. Maybe…
迪恩 她觉得我是个彻底的疯子
Dean, she thought I was a stark raving lunatic.
- 你救了她的命 - 可她不知道
- You saved her life. - Yeah, but she doesn't know that.
知道吗 你们的车
You know, for a stakeout…
用来监视可有点太显眼了
your car's a bit conspicuous.
- 你们还在这儿干吗？- 说实话？呃…
- What are you still doing here? - Honestly? Uh…
虽然你今晚应该不会变成狼人
We're pretty sure you're not gonna turn tonight…
但我们想百分百的确定 所以 你知道 我们就… 在盯梢
but we gotta be 100 percent. So, you know, we're lurking.
- 我知道这很疯狂 - 当然了
- Look, I know this sounds crazy…Sure does.
不过 要是要等结果…
Well, if we're gonna wait it out…
也许咱们应该一起等
we might as well do it together.
你们说的是真的 对吧
You were telling the truth, weren't you?
所有的事
About everything.
你们所做的 都是为了救我
What you did, it was to help me.
- 对 - 我干了那么多可怕的事…
- Yeah. - I did all those horrible things…
在变成狼人的时候
when I turned.
你并不知道
You didn't know.
那么 你们什么时候能确定？
So when will we know for sure?
- 月亮出来的时候？- 我不觉得
- Moonrise? No, I don't think so.
昨天晚上你是半夜时变的身 我觉得应该等到日出
You turned middle of the night last night. I think we gotta hang in until sunup.
看来得消磨好长一段时间了
Well, it looks like we got ourselves a few hours to kill.
想玩扑克嘛？
Poker, anyone?
哦 你们继续聊
Oh, no, you guys talk.
这 这是不是说明没事了？
Does? Does this mean it worked?
我想是的
Yeah, I think so.
哦 天 谢谢你
Oh, God, thank you.
太谢谢了
Thank you so much.
你也是 迪恩 谢谢
You too, Dean. Thank you.
啊 别客气
don't mention it.
好吧
Yeah.
那 我正好要回旅店
So I'm just gonna head back to the hotel…
看看付费频道什么的
and watch some pay-per-view or something.
真识相
That was smooth.
他没有恶意
He means well.
他是觉得你会和我上床
You mean, he thinks you're gonna get laid.
- 瞧 我… - 没关系
- Look, I… - It's okay.
不
No.
我知道我吓坏你了
I know I scared the crap out of you, all right?
- 我 我是说 - 我把你捆在椅子上
- I mean, I tied you to a chair. - That's right up there with me…
而我把你的脸都抓伤了
scratching up your face.
我们没可能…
There's just no way…
回到原来了 你知道？
we could go back, you know…
回到一切开始之前
before it happened.
你说的对
You're right.
没有办法
There's just no way.
- 她 她变身了 - 什么？
- She turned. - What?
我没能抓住她
I couldn't grab her in time.
我们得找到她 萨姆
We'll find her, Sammy.
我已经打电话问了鲍比 他不知道别的办法
I already called Bobby. He doesn't know anything.
除了切断血脉源不管用
Except, he knew severing the bloodline wouldn't work.
他们都说是没办法复原的
Most everyone says it's impossible to reverse it.
我们和她一起的时候怎么没变？
How come she didn't turn when we were with her?
- 迪恩 - 你和她上床 然后她就变成狼人逃了
- Dean. - You put her to bed, then she wolfed out?
- 也许要在睡着的时候才会变 - 这还有什么关系？
- Maybe she's gotta be asleep to turn? - What does it matter?
我们得想办法救救她 也许漏掉了什么
We gotta find some way to help her. Some legend we missed.
难道我们认识的人会不知道？
If there was, someone we know would've known.
那就更仔细的找 直到找到为止
Well then, we have to look harder until we find something.
萨姆 我不觉得咱们还有别的选择
Sammy, I don't think we got a choice here anymore.
- 什么？- 她是个好女孩
- What? - I hate to say it…
但是她有一部分是…
she's sweet, but part is-
- 邪恶的？- 对
- Evil? - Yeah.
他们也是这么说我的 迪恩 就是说 你不会杀我
That's what they say about me, Dean. So me, you won't kill…
她就可以一枪崩了？
but her, you're just gonna blow away?
- 萨姆？- 麦迪逊 你在哪儿？
- Sam? - Madison. Where are you?
我不 不知道在哪儿
I don't-I don't-I don't know where I am.
有街道标志么？呃…
Well, do you see any street signs?
有 有 在米德尔 波因特
Yeah, yeah. Middlepoint.
好 好 等我 麦迪 我们去找你 呆在那儿别动
All right, all right. Hold on, Maddy. We're coming to get you. Just stay where you are.
我什么也不记得
I don't remember anything.
昨晚我可能杀了人
I probably killed someone last night.
对吗？
Didn't I?
我们还不知道
There's no way to know yet.
有什么别的办法能治好？
Is there something else we can try to make it go away?
我们会想出办法的 肯定在什么地方 会有办法的
We'll find something. I mean, there's gotta be some answer, somewhere.
不完全是真的
That's not entirely true.
麦迪逊 你应该知道
Madison, you deserve to know.
我们查过所有的方法
We've scoured every source.
就是找不到让你复原的办法
There's just no cure.
他说的是真的？
Is…? Is he right?
也许晚上可以把你关起来 但是…
I mean, we could lock you up at night…
你会逃出来 总有一天你会…
but you'd bust out, and some night you will…
杀了别人
someone else dies.
真的很抱歉
I'm sorry, I am.
看来就是这样了
So I guess that's all there is to it, then.
- 别这样 别这么说 - 萨姆 我不想再伤害别人了
- Stop it. Don't talk like that. - Sam, I don't wanna hurt anyone else.
我不想伤害你
I don't wanna hurt you.
放下枪
Put that down.
我自己做不到
I can't do it myself.
我要你帮我
I need you to help me.
麦迪逊
Madison.
- 不行 - 萨姆
- No. - Sam.
- 我是个怪物 - 你不是
- I'm a monster. You don't have to be.
我们能找到办法的 好么？
We can find a way, all right?
- 我能 我会救你的 - 你试过了
- I can. I'm gonna save you. - You tried.
我知道你试过了
I know you tried.
这是最后的办法了
This is all there is left.
帮帮我 萨姆
Help me, Sam.
我要你来动手
I want you to do it.
- 我希望是你 - 我做不到
- I want it to be you. - I can't.
我不想死
I don't wanna die.
真的
I don't.
但是我不能这样活着
But I can't live like this.
这样你才能救我
This is the way you can save me.
请你
Please.
请你救救我
I'm asking you to save me.
萨姆
Sam.
- 对不起 - 不 你说的对
- I'm sorry. - No, you're right.
她也是
She's right.
- 萨姆 让我来 - 她要我去做
- Sammy, I got this one. I'll do it. - She asked me to.
- 你不用这样 - 必须我来
- You don't have to. - Yes, I do.
求你了
Please.
在这等着
Just wait here.